motivateus.com 2018-05-05

# Privacy Policy - Motivating Moments

|  Motivating Moments LLC respects the privacy concerns of the users of its Internet Site called Motivating Moments. We have two web addresses that point to the same Motivating Moments website - www.motivateus.com and www.motivatingmoments.com.

Protecting your privacy is of the utmost importance to us; and keeping your information secure is one of our top priorities. We will never sell or divulge in any way any personally identifiable information to a third party without your prior consent, unless we are lawfully required to do so. We safeguard information about you according to established and commercially reasonable security standards and procedures. We take privacy and security matters very seriously; and it is important to us that you understand and are comfortable with our privacy standards. We want to make your experience on our website as enjoyable and rewarding as possible.

Motivating Moments LLC requests that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.

By visiting, submitting or subscribing to a Motivating Moments web site you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of our Site, or your dealings with our Site, you can contact us through e-mail: helping@motivateus.com

You may also contact us at :  
Motivating Moments LLC  
1085 Shady Lane  
Waterford, Michigan 48327 USA

**What information of yours does the Motivating Moments collect & How is it Used?**

Information collected online is usually defined as being either anonymous or personally identifiable. 

Anonymous information refers to data that cannot be tied back to a specific individual. For example, Motivating Moments LLC collects some information each time a visitor comes to our website. Motivating Moments LLC collects the visitor's IP address (e.g., whether the user is logged on from att.com or aol.com), referral data (e.g., the Internet address of the last Web page visited by a user before clicking over to our website site), and browser and platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Windows platform). Motivating Moments LLC collects this user information for purposes of website monitoring, improvement, and targeted advertising. You do not have to register with the Motivating Moments LLC before we can collect this anonymous information.

Personally identifiable information refers to data that tells us specifically who you are, such as your name and email address, which may be collected in addition to the anonymous data described above. Motivating Moments LLC collects personal information in the following ways from different parts of its Web site:

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Submission Forms**  
Our Submission form on our website requests that you give us contact information including first name or initial, last name or initial, email address, demographic information (state/province, country) and profile data (age).

Contact information we collect from our forms (such as your email address) is used to process your submission for publication requests. The contact information is also used to get in touch with you when necessary regarding your submission(s).

**Responses to Email Inquiries**  
When Visitors or Members send email inquiries to Motivating Moments LLC, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. Motivating Moments LLC does not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with any third party.

**Voluntary Customer Surveys**  
We may periodically conduct both visitor and member surveys. We encourage our visitors and members to participate in these surveys because they provide us with important information that helps us to improve the types of services we offer and how we provide them to you. Your personal information and responses will remain strictly confidential, even if the survey is conducted by a third party. Participation in our surveys is voluntary.

We take the information we receive from individuals and members responding to our Surveys and combine (or aggregate) it to create broader, generic responses to the survey questions (such as gender, age, geographic location, hobbies, education, employment, industry sector, or other demographic information). We then use the aggregated information to improve the quality of our services to you, and to develop new services and products. This aggregated, non-personally identifying information may be shared with third parties.

**Disclosures, Cookies and Web Beacons**

**Disclosures:**  
We are a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites. Please make the assumption that any products or services may be affiliate links. 

What are affiliate links?   
Links to merchants that are used to sell or promote someone else's product or service. If you purchase items through our links, we will earn a commission You will not pay more when buying a product through our links, in fact sometimes we are able to negotiate a lower rate or bonuses that are not available elsewhere. Plus, when you order through our links, you allow us to continue to offer free stuff. We definitely appreciate your support!

Did you know that we also participate in allowing advertising on our site? Advertising and purchases made through our affiliate links provide some income and allow us to devote time and energy to the growth and upkeep of motivateus.com and future web properties.

Motivating Moments LLC does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

"We allow third-party companies to collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or a third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice, you can visit www.networkadvertising.org."

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**   
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/ 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include but are not limited to ....  
Google Adsense  
Commission Junction  
Clickbank  
Linkshare  
Amazon  
Kontera

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Motivating Moments LLC's websites send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Motivating Moments LLC's websites privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

**Choice/Opt-Out:**  
You always have the option of removing your name from any email list to not receive future communications. To ensure immediate removal from any of our communications send us an email at helping@motivateus.com with a copy of the undesired email attached to the request and state your wish to be removed from the mailing list.

**Special Circumstances**  
It is Motivating Moments LLC's policy not to use or share the personal information about Visitors, submitters or members in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

However, Motivating Moments LLC may disclose personal information about Visitors, submitters or members, or information regarding your use of the Web sites for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be who may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with Motivating Moments LLC's rights or property, other Motivating Moments LLC web site users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities, violating our Terms of Use Policy or other user policies; to operate the Website properly; or to protect Motivating Moments LLC and our members.

The practices and policies for the URL: www.motivateus.com are the same as the practices and policies of the URL: www.motivatingmoments.com.

**Security:**  
Security for all personally identifiable information is extremely important to us. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Motivating Moments LLC cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

**Motivating Moments LLC Commitment to Children's Privacy**  
Protecting children's privacy is especially important to us. It is our policy to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA") and all other applicable laws. Please read our Children's Privacy Policy.

We have Web pages designed especially for our younger users, primarily teens. While we make every effort to ensure that these Web sites are fun and age-appropriate for our younger audience, we believe that there is no substitute for proper parental supervision. 

If a child under the age of 13 wishes to submit a quote, story, or poem to our website, a parental permission form first has to be filled out and faxed to: 248-681-6401 att: Motivating Moments LLC.

Once the form is received, the parent will receive an email, confirming the receipt of the form and the submission or subscription process can proceed.

To submit a quote, story or poem, please go with your child to http://www.motivateus.com/form.htm

**Links to Other Sites:**  
Motivating Moments LLC is not responsible for the content or practices of third party websites that may be linked to our Sites. Our Sites may also be linked to websites operated by other companies. Visitors to these web sites should refer to each web site's respective privacy policies and practices.

**Your Acceptance of These Terms:**  
By using Motivating Moments LLC's Motivating Moments website, you signify your acceptance of the Motivating Moments LLC Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Motivating Moments website. Motivating Moments LLC reserves the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this policy at any time, so visitors, submitters and members are encouraged to review this policy from time to time. Your continued use of the Motivating Moments LLC's Motivating Moments website following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

Last update March 20, 2017

Copyright © 2017 Motivating Moments LLC.   
All Rights Reserved. 

|   
---|---|---  
  
**Have something you would like to share?  
An insight that has helped you?  
We invite you to submit a quote.**
